<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entrepreneurship on Rian&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on Rian&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 12:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on a startup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cherry_reflections/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cherry_reflections/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the last 18 months I&amp;rsquo;ve been building a startup, but we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to close it down. It was a tough decision, but the right one. Even though it failed, I have only minor regrets. The company failed to grow, but I experienced personal growth that would be unachievable in a regular job. Would I do it again? Yes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cherry Recommends was a SaaS platform (not really, but the term&amp;rsquo;s in vogue) for improving the effectiveness of promotions in e-commerce. We used machine learning algorithms to target individual customers with &amp;ldquo;the best&amp;rdquo; promotion. When used in properly, Cherry could increase revenue (yes, &lt;em&gt;revenue&lt;/em&gt;) by 15%. Honestly, we thought it was pretty cool. It was ugly, it was hard to use, and hard to explain - but with financial outcomes like that, we were confident we&amp;rsquo;d find a way. But after 9 months of searching, we just weren&amp;rsquo;t able to acquire new customers at anything near the required rate. We tried changing the our target customer, changing our brand, changing our messaging, and changing our pricing. But those things weren&amp;rsquo;t the problem. The problem was simple: people did not want to buy our product.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
