<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The-Battle-for-Eurasia on Rian&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/the-battle-for-eurasia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The-Battle-for-Eurasia on Rian&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 20:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/the-battle-for-eurasia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Battle for Eurasia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-battle-for-eurasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-battle-for-eurasia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The pieces are moving; the battle for Eurasia has begun.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 20th century saw the the first global wars. Before the onset of the great war, European powers dominated the globe through superior technology, particularly in war. Two world wars later, and the balance of power had shifted dramatically.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Orthodox interpretation of the post war period proposes a war of ideologies between capitalism and collectivism. But this was essentially a collective brainwashing by the two major powers of the era: the Soviet Union and the United States. In the west, the narrative goes something like: &lt;em&gt;capitalism and democracy are fundamentally connected, and are better than communism&lt;/em&gt;. However, this interpretation entirely fails to account for the role of China in the fall of the USSR.&#xA;In 1971 Kissinger traveled to China, initiating a secret strategic relationship between the emerging Chinese Communist-led state and the Americans. In Chinese terms, using the far away enemy against the near enemy. The Sino-Soviet split became a dagger to the heart of soviet communism. The Soviet Union, which became heavily militarised and surrounded by enemies, could not sustain both its economy and military in such a hostile environment. What followed was victory for the Americans and the Chinese. Once again, orthodox interpretation of the fall resembles Fukuyama. But events in the early 21st century throw new challenges to the end of history. History, rather than ending, provides new challenges.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
